Finding Aid for Jens Jensen Drawings and Papers 1903-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Drawings
  - F
    - Fearing, Joseph L., Highland Park, Illinois
      - Plat of survey..., 1916; FEA1; Blueprint; location, dimensions of property; original unsigned. 21 x 28 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
    - Fischer, John, Kewanee, Illinois
      - Grading around pool of the John Fischer estate, 1918; FIC1; Pencil on tracing paper; notes; unsigned; blueline., 34 x 57 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Grading around pool of the John Fischer estate, 1918; FIC1a; Two sheets; appears to be print of 1, blueline., 34 x 57 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - A planting plan for the property of Mr. John Fischer, 1918; FIC2; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; signed. 84 x 71 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Plan and elevations of tea house and trellis., 1918; FIC3; Ink on linen; signed; blueline., 32 x 45 cm. Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Plan and elevations of tea house and trellis., 1918; FIC3a; Appears to be print of 3, blueline., 32 x 45 cm. Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - A planting plan of rose garden for Mr. John Fisher [sic]., 1918; FIC4; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amount of plantings; signed. 39 x 41 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Cross section of pool for Mr. John Fischer, 1918; FIC 5; Ink on linen; note ""For plan of Pool refar [sic] (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Cross section of pool for Mr. John Fischer, 1918; FIC5a; Ink on linen; note ""For plan of Pool refar [sic] (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
      - Details of bird bath. Garden of Mr. John Fischer, 1918; FIC6; Ink on linen; signed. 33 x 29 cm. scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 32)
    - Fish, F.S., "Sunnyside." South Bend, Indiana
      - Survey of Sunnyside, 1924; FIH1; Blueprint; residences and drives for F. S. Fish, J. M. Studebaker, and J. M. Studebaker, Jr.; unsigned. 90 x 122 cm. scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - A preliminary sketch for Sunnyside, 1924; FIH2; Pencil on tracing paper; plan of Fish and Studebaker residences, buildings, gardens, roadways (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - A preliminary sketch of planting with existing drives at Sunnyside, 1924; FIH3; Pencil on tracing paper; signed. 95 x 68 cm. scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - A planting plan for the gardens at Sunnyside, 1925; FIH4; Pencil, ink on linen; location, type of plantings; revisions in pencil; buildings, gardens; unsigned. 146 x 75 cm. scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - A planting plan for the vegetable garden., 1926; FIH5; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; unsigned. 58 x 64 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
    - Fisher, C.T., Oakland County, Michigan
      - Planting plan for the entrance [sic] of the estate of C. T. Fisher, 1929; FIR1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; signed. 166 x 102 cm. cale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Profile of road at bridge [sic]. Estate of Mr. C. T. Fisher, FIR2; Ink on linen; indicates present and proposed grades, with elevations; unsigned. 108 x 57 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Proposal for lake. Estate of Mr. C. T. Fisher, FIR3; Ink on linen; cut, fill instructions; notes; unsigned. 110 x 66 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - House plan. Dixiana Farm, FIR4; Pencil on tracing paper; unsigned. 40 x 37 cm. scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Dixiana Farm, FIR5; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of some plantings; notes; unsigned. 102 x 85 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
    - Fisher, Walter L, Hubbard Woods, Illinois
      - Topographical survey of estate of Mr. Walter L. Fisher, 1914; FIW1; Ink on linen; selected elevations; location, type of existing trees; unsigned. 112 x 66 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Grounds of Mr. Walter L. Fisher....Sketch, 1914; FIW2; Pencil on tracing paper; signed. 94 x 60 cm. scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Grounds of Mr. Walter L. Fisher...Planting plan, 1914; FIW3; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; notes in pencil at middle left; signed. 108 x 65 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Plan for grape arbor. Grounds of W. L. Fisher, Esq., 1915; FIW4; Pencil on tracing paper; plan, elevations; notes; signed. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Revised planting plan. Mr. W. L. Fisher...planting along road, 1915; FIW5; Ink on linen; unsigned. 28 x 63 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
    - Florsheim, Harold M., Ravinia, Illinois (Eugene H. Klaber and Ernest A. Greensfeld Jr., architect)
      - House for Mr. Harold Florsheim...First floor plan, 1925; FLO1; Blueprint; Eugene H. Klaber and Ernest A. Grunsfeld, Jr., architects; unsigned. 74 x 60 cm. scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Plan of pool for Mr. H. Florsheim, FLO2; Ink on linen; unsigned. 71 x 46 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Topographical survey of lots 3 and 4 in the subdivision of lot 121 South Highland addition to Highland Park in sec. 36 T. 43 N. R. 12 E. of the 3rd P. M. [at bottom] Survey for Harold Florsheim, FLO3; Blueprint; topo lines, elevations; survey by ""Windes and Marsh, Engineers and Surveyors, Winnetka, Illinois""; note on reverse, ""H. M. Florsheim, 541 W. Adams St., Chicago, Illinois""; unsigned. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
        (neg. # JEN-Flo-3)
      - Plot plan, FLO4; Blueprint; reduced sketch of property in FLO2, with outline of residence, buildings, driveway, locations of trees and topo lines; in pencil at lower right, ""Florsheim""; unsigned. 73 x 52 cm. Scale: 1/2"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
        (neg. # JEN-Flo-4)
      - Florsheim Topo, FLO5; Pencil on tracing paper; title scribbled along top edge; topo lines; unsigned. 121 x 92 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - A preliminary sketch. Estate of Mr. Harold M. Florsheim, FLO6; Pencil on heavy paper; plan of gardens, pool, plantings; list of twelve ""things to do"" on estate (e. g. ""Plant heavy north line""); unsigned. 77 x 73 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
        (neg. # JEN-Flo-6)
    - Florsheim, Irving, Highland Park, Illinois
      - Preliminary sketch for the estate of Irving Florsheim, 1929; FLR1; Pencil on tracing paper; location of house, roadways, paddocks, trees, pool; in red, plan for drain tiles; at lower right, estimates for tile ($1500) and border planting ($2316); unsigned. 95 x 50 cm. Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
      - Untitled, 1929; FLR2; Pencil on tracing paper; similar to FLR1, with addition garden areas replacing buildings on other side of circular drive; unsigned (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
    - Folds, Charles
      - A planting plan for the property of Mr. Charles Folds, 1923; FOC1; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; footpaths; garden; signed. 71 x 48 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 33)
    - Ford, Edsel B., Seal Harbor, Maine (Duncan Candler, architect)
      - Topography near the summit of Ox Hill. Ford estate, 1922; FOE1; Blueprint, red, black pencil; residence, drive, walks in pencil over topo plan; unsigned. 105 x 88 cm. Scale: 1"" = 8' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE1)
      - General surroundings of estate of Edsel Ford, Esq., 1923; FOE2; Blueprint, some pencil additions; roads, residence, some contour lines; (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE2)
      - House for Edsel Ford, Esq...Southwest Elevation., 1923; FOE3; Blueprint; note, ""Suggested treatment for living hall windows and living room arbor""; Duncan Candler, architect; unsigned. 78 x 30 cm. Scale: 1/8"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE3)
      - House for Edsel Ford, Esq...General plan, 1924; FOE4; Blueprint; pencil additions, markings on portions of grounds; Duncan Candler, architect; unsigned. 77 x 70 cm. Scale: 3/32"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE4)
      - A plan showing rock work and earth fill. The garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford. Sheet No. 1, 1924; FOE5; Ink and pencil on linen; plan and several section elevations; at lower right, number 4 in pencil; unsigned (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE5)
      - A planting plan for the garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1925; FOE6; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; at lower left, number 2 in ink; signed. 82 x 44 cm. Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE6)
      - A planting plan for the estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1925; FOE7; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; many notes; residence by Duncan Candler; at lower right, number 3 in ink; signed. 92 x 68 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE7)
      - Survey of Lawrence Cottage. Estate of Edsel B. Ford, 1925; FOE8; Ink on linen; location of ledges, trees, boulders, paths, walls; dimensions of cottage; note under title, ""made by (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE8)
      - A planting plan for the picking garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1925; FOE9; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; at lower right, number 7 in pencil; signed. 61 x 36 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE9)
      - A revised planting plan for the picking garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1926; FOE10; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of plantings; at lower right, number 6 in pencil; signed. 61 x 28 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
        (neg. # FOE10)
    - Edsel B. Ford, Gaukler Pointe, Macomb County, Michigan
      - A plan of the water system. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1926; FOE11; Ink on linen; water pipes and dimensions; at lower right, ""Sheet E-1""; penciled notes at left; unsigned. (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A plan of the drainage system. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1926; FOE12; Ink on linen; at lower right, ""Sheet E-2""; unsigned. 143 x 95 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A grading plan. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1926; FOE13; Ink on linen; elevations; at lower right, ""sheet E-4""; signed. 143 x 95 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - Profile of main drive. Estate of Edsel B. Ford, 1927; FOE14; Ink on linen; present and finished elevations; at lower right, ""TMLJ Rod- (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A grading plan for the house area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1927; FOE15; Ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; at lower right, ""sheet E-5""; unsigned; 97 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A plan of water and drainage system in the garden area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1927; FOE16; Ink on linen; at lower right, "" Sheet E-6""; unsigned; 128 x 94 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - Section thru centerline of gardens. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1927; FOE17; Ink on graph-lined linen; cross-section view of picking garden, playground... (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A planting plan for the areas north from the residence to section line 14 and from the lake to section line D. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1927; FOE18; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""Sheet No. P-1""; signed; 132 x 88 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A planting plan for the northern end of the meadow. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1927; FOE19; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""Sheet P-2""; signed; 144 x 96 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A planting plan for the vegetable garden area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1927; FOE20; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; at lower right, ""Sheet P-3""; signed; (Map-case 51, Folder 34)
      - A drainage and water plan for the vegetable garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE21; Ink on linen; notes; at lower right, ""Sheet # E-10""; unsigned; 95 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A plan of the rock work. Swimming pool. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE22; Ink on linen; elevations; at lower right, ""Sheet E-9""; unsigned; 80 x 45 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A revised plan of the water system. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE23; Ink on linen; at lower right, ""Sheet E-1-A""; unsigned; 140 x 82 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for the south portion of the estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE24; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""Sheet P-5""; unsigned; 83 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for the island. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE25; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""Sheet P-5""; 83 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for the island. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. ford., 1928; FOE26; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""P-10,""... (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
        (neg. # FOE26)
      - A plan of the water system. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1928; FOE27; Blueprint; unsigned; 150 x 85 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan of the garden area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE28; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; at lower right, ""Sheet-P-6""; unsigned; 133 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
        (neg. # FOE28)
      - A planting plan for the garden area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1928; FOE29; Ink on linen; at lower right, ""P-7"" in pencil; unsigned (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for the rose garden of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1929; FOE30; Red, black ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; notes; at lower right, ""Plan Number P-8""; signed; 102 x 81 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A plan for the planting around swimming pool. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, 1929; FOE31; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; in lower right, ""P-9""; signed; 74 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Proposed changes of the garden area. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1929; FOE32; Pencil on tracing paper; in lower right, ""P-13""; unsigned (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Fountain on the estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1929; FOE33; Pencil on tracing paper; plan; unsigned; 27 x 49 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, 1929; FOE34; Ink on tracing paper; sketch of frog-figure for fountain; unsigned; 41 x 23 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Plan of drainage system. Edsel B. Ford Estate., 1930; FOE35; Blueprint; unsigned; 142 x 73 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for housekeepers cottage. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1930; FOE36; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 90 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan for Jefferson Avenue roadside along the estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford., 1931; FOE37; Ink, pencil on linen; indicates only location of trees, but only one type; at lower right, ""4"" in pencil; 140 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 80' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - A planting plan. Children's play house. Mr. Edsel B. Ford Estate., 1932; FOE38; Ink on linen; no types of plantings indicated (two types sketched in pencil); at lower right, ""P-11"" in pencil; signed; 71 x 55 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Plan of the pool floor showing grades of finished floor. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, FOE39; Ink on graph-lined linen; notes, elevations, cross-sections; note refers to sheet E-3 for construction detail (not in this collection); at lower right, ""Sheet E-8""; unsigned; 98 x 52 cm.; No scale (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE40; Yellow, black ink on linen; appears to be plan for garden, with distances; at lower right, ""Sheet E-11""; unsigned; 47 x 27 cm.; No scale (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE41; Pencil, ink on graph-lined paper; plan for rose garden, detailed elevations of walls, penciled sketches of cross-sections of garden; at lower right, ""E-13"" in pencil; unsigned; 105 x 56 cm. (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE42; Red, black ink on linen; plan and elevations of rose garden, terraces and walls, with elevations and distances; at lower right, ""E-14"" in pencil; unsigned; 108 x 77 cm.; Scale for some details: 1"" = 2' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Plan of steel edgeing [sic] for rose garden. Estate of Mr. Edsel B. Ford, FOE43; Ink on linen; distances; at lower right, ""E-15"" in pencil; unsigned; 31 x 32 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE44; Pencil on paper; perspective sketch of rose garden and another garden; unsigned; 107 x 44 cm.; No scale (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE45; Pencil on tracing paper; perspective sketch of rose garden and another garden; unsigned; 42 x 26 cm.; No scale (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE46; Pencil on paper; plan of garden and surrounding area, with buildings, trees, pool; unsigned; 104 x 66 cm.; No scale (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
      - Untitled, FOE47; Pencil on tracing paper; two sheets; plan of plantings around pool and road on portion of estate; unsigned; 89 x 36 cm. (both sheets); Scale: 1"" = 20'; (Map-case 51, Folder 35)
    - Ford, Henry. Hotel., Michigan (Albert Kahn, architect)
      - Plot plan showing drives, walks, also finished grades and locations of light standards. Hotel of Mr. Henry Ford., 1930; FOF1; Blueprint; trees marked in yellow; Albert Kahn architect; unsigned; 78 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 32' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Map showing proposed property lines, Ford Hotel., 1930; FOF2; Blueprint; location of plantings; unsigned; 59 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Study - drive and parking space at rear. Hotel for Mr. Henry Ford., 1931; FOF3; ; Blueprint; Albert Kahn, architect; unsigned; 56 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 32' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Sketch showing revised court and drives at rear. Hotel for Mr. Henry Ford., 1931; FOF4; Two sheets; blueprint; perspective sketch of court and plan of court and drives; Albert Kahn, architect; unsigned; 42 x 23 and 43 x 33 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Plan showing revised roadways and rear court. Hotel for Mr. Henry Ford., 1931; FOF5; Blueprint; Albert Kahn, architect; unsigned; 57 x 41 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 32' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Plan showing revised walks and drives. Hotel for Mr. Henry Ford., 1931; FOF6; Blueprint; Albert Kahn, architect; unsigned; 64 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1/32"" = 1' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Tractor buildings for Henry Ford and son, inc...Plot plan., 1919; FOF7; Blueprint; location of buildings, grades; Frederick G. Mueller, architect; Walter R. Hair, associate; unsigned; 98 x 38 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 100' (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
    - Ford Subdivision
      - Untitled, FOJ1; Blueprint; plan, sections, details for layout and construction of several streets; street names: Nowlan, Haigh, Laphan, Molony, Nina, Park; name used as main entry given on verso of sheet; right corner torn away, unsigned. 98 x 74 cm. Scales vary. (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Grading and sidewalk layout. Park Ave. between Haigh [and Lapham], FOJ2; Blueprint; unsigned. 142 x 32 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
      - Grading and sidewalk layout., FOJ3; Blueprint; terrace section right third of sheet torn away; unsigned. 96 x 41 cm. No scale. (Map-case 51, Folder 36)
    - Forestville School, Chicago, Illinois
      - Plat of the tape survey of area around the Forestville School. Champain Avenue and 45th Street., 1916; FOR1; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amount of plantings; signed. 90 x 80 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
    - Frank, Jacob, Chicago, Illinois
      - Sketch showing change of roadway. Residence of Mr. Jacob Frank, 1911; FRA1; Ink, pencil on tracing paper; notes and changes in residence design sketched in pencil; signed. 62 x 32 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
      - New roadway for residence of Mr. Jacob Franks [sic]. N.W. corner of 51st street and Ellis Ave., 1911; FRA2; Pencil on tracing paper; detailed plan and sections; signed. 97 x 60 cm. Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
    - Frawley, Mrs. F.D., Indianapolis, Indiana
      - Untitled, 1922; FRE1; Blueprint, pencil additions; survey, with topo lines, elevations; unsigned. (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
        (neg. # JEN-Fre-1)
      - Revised planting plan for the north side of house of Mrs. F. D. Frawley, 1923; FRE2; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; unsigned. 67 x 39 cm. Scale: 1"" = 39 cm. (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
        (neg. # JEN-Fre-2)
      - A planting plan for the property. Mrs. F. D. Frawley, 1924; FRE3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed. 103 x 58 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
        (neg. # JEN-Fre-3)
      - Plan showing rockwork in the garden of Mrs. F. D. Frawley, FRE4; Yellow, black ink on linen; plan and detailed cross-section of pool; unsigned. 43 x 48 cm. Scales vary (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
        (neg. # JEN-Fre-4)
      - Untitled, FRE5; Blueprint, pencil additions; plan of house; unsigned. 60 x 40 cm. No scale. (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
        (neg. # JEN-Fre-5)
    - Friedman, Mrs. I.K, Winnetka, Illinois.
      - Planting plan for grounds of Mrs. I. K. Friedman., 1911; FRI1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed. 78 x 38 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
    - Friestedt, M.L.P., Lake Bluff, Illinois
      - Friestedt's addition to Lake Bluff., 1909; FRM1; Blueprint, pencil; plat of survey; unsigned. 62 x 48 cm. No scale. (Map-case 52, Folder 37)
  - G
    - Gads Hill Encampment, Lake Bluff, Illinois
      - Gads Hill Encampment, 1909; GAD1; Ink on linen; location of buildings, water pipes, camp sites, etc.; location, type of plantings; signed. 130 x 27 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
    - Garden, Hugh M.G., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Plat of survey and topography of Lot 21, GAH1; Blueprint; unsigned. 57 x 48 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
    - Garden
      - A planting design for a garden, 1924; GAN1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; location of walkways, pool, trellises, seats, etc.; signed. 44 x 43 cm. Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
    - Gary, John W., Glencoe, Illinois (Perkins, Fellows & Will, architect)
      - Estate of Mr. J. W. Gary...Water Pipe plan, 1912; GAR1; Pencil on tracing paper; residence by F. W. Perkins; signed. 52 x 100 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
      - Topo plan. Grounds of Mr. J. W. Gary., 1912; GAR2; Ink on linen; location of select trees; elevations; residence by F. W. Perkins; unsigned. 59 x 104 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
      - Planting plan. Estate of Mr. John W. Gary., 1913; GAR3; Ink on linen; indicates areas to be filled with shrubs; residence by F. W. Perkins; signed. 56 x 97 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
      - Planting plan. Estate of Mr. J. W. Gary....Formal garden, 1913; GAR4; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; notes; residence by F. W. Perkins; signed. 39 x 33 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
      - Estate of J. W. Gary...Location of drive., 1913; GAR5; Red, black ink on linen; plan, with distances; road cross-section, with construction materials; signed. 48 x 34 cm. Scales vary (Map-case 52, Folder 38)
    - Gatzert, August, Glencoe, Illinois.
      - Plat of survey, 1916; GAT1; photocopy of plat (blackline print); surveyed by F. J. Geraghty; unsigned. 45 x 27 cm. No scale. (Map-case 52, Folder 38)